('2-2', 'RACHEL')从北京起飞的第457号班机已经降落
Flight number 457 from Beijing now arriving.
('2-2', 'RACHEL')我的天啊
Oh, my God!
('2-2', 'RACHEL')天啊
('2-2', 'RACHEL')借过
Excuse me.
('2-2', 'RACHEL')借过  借过  有急事  拜托
Move, move, move! Emergency, please!
('2-2', 'RACHEL')借过  借过
Excuse me, excuse me.
('2-2', 'RACHEL')瑞秋
Rache!
('2-4', 'RACHEL')你们在那里啊
There you are!
('2-4', 'RACHEL')那  那...
So, so....
('2-4', 'RACHEL')中国怎么样  老兄
How was China? You!
('2-5', 'ROSS')很棒
It was great.
('2-5', 'ROSS'),('2-6', 'RACHEL')-你怎么了  -什么怎么了
,- What happened?  - What?
('2-7', 'ROSS'),('2-8', 'RACHEL')-你在流血  -是吗  -天呐
,- You're bleeding. - I am? -Oh, my god!
('2-8', 'RACHEL')还真是  我是在流血
Oh, look at that! Yes, I am.
('2-8', 'RACHEL')别管我了  别管我了  游过东方的旅人
Enough about me, enough about me, Mr. Back From The Orient!
('2-8', 'RACHEL')我要听一切事情   什么都不要漏掉
Come on, I wanna hear everything! Everything!
('2-9', 'ROSS')从哪里说起呢
Well, where do I start?
('2-9', 'ROSS')这位是朱莉  朱莉  这位是瑞秋
This is Julie. Julie, this is Rachel.
('2-10', 'RACHEL')这些
These are....
These are...
('2-10', 'RACHEL')不是要给你的
...aren't for you.
('2-10', 'RACHEL')这些是要送给你的
These are for you.
('2-10', 'RACHEL')欢迎光临敝国
Welcome to our country.
('2-11', 'JULIE')谢谢  我是纽约人
Thank you. I'm from New York.
('2-12', 'RACHEL')没关系  那我用它来止血
No problem. We'll use them to stop the bleeding.
('2-12', 'RACHEL'),('2-12', 'RACHEL'),('2-12', 'RACHEL')-好了  去拿行李吧  -好  -好
,,- O.K. Baggage claim? - O.K. - O.K.
('3-2', 'MONICA')她去了机场  准备跟罗斯坦白了
I'm telling you.She went to the airport, and she's gonna go for it with Ross.
('3-3', 'PHOEBE')天啊  这是大事
Oh, my God! This is huge!
('3-3', 'PHOEBE')真是天大的事  真是
This is bigger than huge. This is....
('3-3', 'PHOEBE')什么事算天大的事
All right, what's bigger than huge?
('3-4', 'JOEY'),('3-5', 'PHOEBE')-这件事吗  -对
,- This? - Yes.
('3-6', 'MONICA')喂  你们剪头发了
Guys, you got new haircuts!
('3-7', 'CHANDLER')是的  布菲美发大师的杰作
Yes, we did. Thanks to Vidal Buffay.
('3-8', 'PHOEBE')你们也知道  "你不好看  我们也没面子"
Because, you know, "lf you don't look good, we don't look good."
('3-8', 'PHOEBE')我喜欢这声音
I love that voice!
('3-8', 'PHOEBE')各位
You guys!
('3-8', 'PHOEBE')瑞秋
Rachel.
('3-9', 'RACHEL')机场  机场  罗斯
Airport. Airport. Ross.
('3-9', 'RACHEL')不是一个人
Not alone.
('3-9', 'RACHEL')朱莉
Julie.
('3-9', 'RACHEL')搂着她
Arm around her!
('3-9', 'RACHEL')抽筋  抽筋  抽筋
Cramp! Cramp! Cramp!
('3-10', 'CHANDLER')她好像想说什么
I think she's trying to tell us something.
('3-10', 'CHANDLER')快  猜动词
Quick, get the verbs.
('3-11', 'RACHEL')你  你
You! You!
('3-11', 'RACHEL')你说他喜欢我
You said he liked me!
('3-11', 'RACHEL')你  你
You! You!
('3-11', 'RACHEL')你这个慢郎中
You slowpokes!
('3-12', 'ROSS')没关系  瑞秋  我们拿了行李
That's all right. Rache. We got the bags.
('3-12', 'ROSS')你们好啊
Hi, hello!
('3-12', 'ROSS')朱莉  这是我妹妹  摩妮卡
Julie, this is my sister, Monica.
('3-12', 'ROSS')这是钱德勒
This is Chandler.
('3-12', 'ROSS')菲比  嗨
Phoebe, hi.
('3-12', 'ROSS'),('3-13', 'JOEY')-乔伊  你好吗  -好啊
,- Joey. What up? - What up?!
('3-14', 'ROSS')各位  这位是朱莉
Everyone, this is Julie.
('3-15', 'RACHEL')朱莉
Julie.
('3-17', 'JULIE')但我还没到  你们见到的不是我本人
But I'm not here, you haven't met me.
('3-17', 'JULIE')今天不用飞二十小时
I'll make a better impression tommorrow
('3-17', 'JULIE')我明天会让大家耳目一新
when I don't have 20 hours of plane on me.
('3-18', 'ROSS'),('3-19', 'JULIE')-还有巴士  -天啊
,- And bus. - Oh, my God!
('3-20', 'ROSS'),('3-21', 'JULIE')-那个尖叫的家伙  -还有他吐的口水
,- With the screaming guy - And the spitting.
('3-22', 'ROSS')你们一定要听这个故事
You gotta hear this story.
('3-23', 'JULIE')我们坐的巴士一定有两百岁了
We're on this bus that's  easily 200 years old.
('3-24', 'ROSS')至少两百岁
Two hundred, at least.
('3-25', 'JULIE'),('3-26', 'RACHEL')-那人  -还有一只鸡在她腿上拉屎
,- And this guy... - And the chicken poops in her lap!
('3-26', 'RACHEL')对不起
I'm so sorry.
('3-26', 'RACHEL')我直接说出了结尾  对不对
I just gave away the ending, didn't I?
('3-26', 'RACHEL')我刚在计程车上听了这个故事
I just heard this story in the cab...
('3-26', 'RACHEL')满脑子想的都是这个
...and it is all I can think about.
('3-27', 'MONICA')真让人吃惊
This is amazing.
('3-27', 'MONICA')怎么发生的
How... how did this happen?
('3-28', 'JULIE')罗斯与我一起读过研究生
Rose and I were in grad school together.
('3-29', 'ROSS')后来就没有再见面  我降落在中国机场时
We haven't seen each other since then. I land in China...
('3-29', 'ROSS')猜猜是谁负责挖掘的
...guess who's in charge of the dig?
('3-30', 'RACHEL')就是朱莉
Julie!
('3-30', 'RACHEL')真是太棒了
Isn't that great?
('3-30', 'RACHEL')真是棒得面红耳赤   棒得有苦说不出
Isn't that just kick-you-in-the-crotch, spit-on-your-neck fantastic?
('3-31', 'MONICA')她习惯这么说话
It's an expression.
('3-32', 'ROSS')我们只是来打个招呼
We just wanted to say a quick hi.
('3-32', 'ROSS'),('3-33', 'JULIE')-然后我们要去看宝宝  -然后睡一觉
,- Then we'll see the baby. - Then we've gonna get some sleep.
('3-34', 'ROSS')现在是中国的明天晚上六点
It's 6:00 tomorrow night, our time.
('3-35', 'CHANDLER')听好了  别告诉我会发生什么事  我喜欢惊喜
OK, well, listen. Don't tell us what's gonna happen. I like being surprised.
('3-36', 'RACHEL'),('3-36', 'RACHEL')-再见   -再见
,- Bye! - Bye!
('4-1', 'ROSS'),('4-2', 'RACHEL')-瑞秋  我想喝点咖啡  谢谢  -没问题
,- Rach. Can I get some coffee? Thank you. - Sure.
('4-4', 'CHANDLER'),('4-5', 'RACHEL')-瑞秋  -你跟他谈了吗
,- Rache. - Did you talk to him yet?
('4-7', 'RACHEL'),('4-7', 'RACHEL')-没有  -那就没咖啡
,- No. - Then, no.
('4-8', 'CHANDLER')你在中国都干了什么
What the hell happened to you in China?
('4-8', 'CHANDLER')你离开前还疯狂爱着  你知道的
When last we left you, you totaly were in love with, you know.
('4-9', 'ROSS')我知道我爱她
I know, I know I was.
('4-9', 'ROSS')但我心里有个声音一直告诉我
But there was always this little voice inside that kept saying:
('4-9', 'ROSS')不可能的  死心吧  知道是谁的声音吗
"It's never gonna happen. Move on." You know whose voice that was?
('4-10', 'CHANDLER')上帝
God?
('4-11', 'ROSS')是你的声音  朋友
It was you, pal.
('4-12', 'CHANDLER')也许是上帝模仿我的声音
Maybe it was God doing me.
('4-13', 'ROSS')你说得对  她只把我当朋友  仅此而已
You were right. She looks at me and sees a friend. That's all.
('4-13', 'ROSS')然后我遇见了朱莉
And then I met Julie... and...
('4-13', 'ROSS')我们在一起非常开心
...and we're having a great time.
('4-13', 'ROSS')要不是因为你  我绝不会跟朱莉在一起
and I have to say.I never would have gone for it with her, if it hadn't been for you.
('4-14', 'CHANDLER')你欠我一个情  大个子
Well, you owe me one, big guy.
('4-15', 'RACHEL')你的柠檬汁
Here's your lemonade.
('4-16', 'ROSS')我没点柠檬汁
I didn't order lemonade
('4-17', 'RACHEL')那你最好送回去  否则他们会要你付钱
You better go take that back because they're gonna charge you for that.
('4-18', 'ROSS'),('4-19', 'RACHEL')-可  -快  快  快去
,- But... - Go, go, go! Come on, come on!
('4-19', 'RACHEL')说吧  你问出了什么
OK. So what did you find out?
('4-20', 'CHANDLER')他说
He said....
('4-20', 'CHANDLER')他说他们在一起很开心
He said they're having a great time.
('4-20', 'CHANDLER')别难过了
I'm sorry.
('4-20', 'CHANDLER')但有好的一面  如果你往好处想
But the silver lining, if you wanna see it...
('4-20', 'CHANDLER')他完全是自己做了这个决定
...is that he made this decision all by himself...
('4-20', 'CHANDLER')完全没有受外人的影响
...without any outside help whatsoever.
('4-21', 'RACHEL')这怎么是好的一面
How is that a silver lining?
('4-22', 'CHANDLER')你要努力往好处想
You have to really wanna see it.
('5-1', 'ROSS')讽刺的是  打比赛时都没人愿意跟他们一队
Ironically, these are the guys who were picked last in gym.
('5-1', 'ROSS')菲比
Hey, Pheebs.
('5-2', 'MONICA')你知道我想什么吗
You know what I'm thinking?
('5-3', 'PHOEBE')好的
Oh, ok.
('5-3', 'PHOEBE')因为
How...
('5-3', 'PHOEBE')你太久没性生活了
...it's been so long since you've had sex
('5-3', 'PHOEBE')你想知道有没有什么改变
you're wondering if they've changed it?
('5-4', 'MONICA')不是  但是我现在是在想这事
No. Although now that's what I'm thinking.
('5-5', 'PHOEBE')你本来在想什么
So what were you thinking?
('5-6', 'MONICA')你帮他们剪头发  我想你也帮我剪剪吧
You gave the guys great haircuts. I thought you'd like to do mine.
('5-7', 'PHOEBE')不行
No.
('5-8', 'MONICA')为什么不行
Why not?
('5-9', 'PHOEBE')因为我
Because I'm just....
('5-9', 'PHOEBE')我非常挑剔  而且是个控制狂
I'm incredibly anal and an unbelievable control freak.
('5-10', 'MONICA')不  你才不是
No, you're not.
('5-11', 'PHOEBE')我知道我不是  不过你是
I know I'm not, but you are.
('5-11', 'PHOEBE')我只是想照顾你的感受
I was trying to spare your feelings.
('5-12', 'JOEY')喂  你好
Hello? Hi.
('5-12', 'JOEY')请等一下
Yes. Hold on a second.
('5-12', 'JOEY')罗斯  朱莉找你
Ross, Julie for you.
('5-12', 'JOEY')谁能介绍一个好裁缝
Anybody know a good tailor?
('5-12', 'JOEY')需要改衣服吗
You need clothes altered?
('5-14', 'CHANDLER')不  我只是要找一个人用粉笔在我身上画线
No, I'm just looking for a man to draw on me with chalk.
('5-16', 'CHANDLER')去找弗兰基  我家人都找他做衣服
Go see Frankie. My family's been going to him forever.
('5-17', 'JOEY')我十五岁时的第一套西装就是他做的
He did my first suit when I was 15.
('5-17', 'JOEY')不  是十六岁
No, wait, 16.
('5-17', 'JOEY')不  对不起  是十五岁
No, excuse me, 15.
('5-17', 'JOEY')1990年是几岁
All right, when was 1990?
('5-18', 'CHANDLER')当你掏耳朵时  碰到东西就要停下来
You have to stop the Q-Tip when there's resistance!
('5-19', 'ROSS')好  好  甜心  待会见
OK, OK, Sweetheart, I'll see you later.
('5-19', 'ROSS')好  再见  什么
Okay, bye. What?
('5-19', 'ROSS')你真好
That is so sweet.
('5-19', 'ROSS')好  不  你先挂
Okay. No, you hang up.
('5-19', 'ROSS')不  你先  好
No, you... Ok, Ok.
('5-19', 'ROSS')一   二   三
One, two, three.
('5-19', 'ROSS')你也没有挂
You didn't hang up either.
('5-20', 'RACHEL')她没挂
She didn't hang up.
('5-21', 'ROSS')好  不  不  你挂电话
Okay, no. No, you hang up.
('5-21', 'ROSS')你挂  你挂  你
You. You. You...
('5-22', 'RACHEL')对不起  我以为你在跟我说话
Sorry, I thought you were talking to me.
('5-23', 'ROSS')瑞秋
Rachel.
('5-23', 'ROSS'),('5-24', 'RACHEL')-我打回去  -好
,- I'll just call her back. - Okay.
('5-25', 'ROSS')甜心  对不起  刚才断线了
Hi, sweetie. I'm sorry. We got disconnected.
('5-25', 'ROSS')不  你挂掉
No, you hang up.
('5-26', 'RACHEL')我到底是怎么回事
How did this happen to me?
('5-26', 'RACHEL')一周前  两周前  我很好
A week ago, two weeks ago, I was fine.
('5-26', 'RACHEL')罗斯只是罗斯  只是一个普通人
Ross was just Ross. Just this guy.
('5-26', 'RACHEL')现在突然间  他不一样了
Now all of a sudden, he's Ross...
('5-26', 'RACHEL')变成这个大帅哥  我却不能和他好
...this really great guy that I can't have.
('5-27', 'MONICA')甜心  我也希望你能和他好
Sweetie, I wanted you to have him too.
('5-28', 'RACHEL')我知道你的心意
I know you did.
('5-28', 'RACHEL')我必须要想办法
I'm just gonna deal with it.
('5-28', 'RACHEL')我必须要离开这里
I gotta get out of here!
('5-29', 'CHANDLER')我不管你们怎么说  她肯定有心事
I don't care what you guys say, something's bothering her.
('6-1', 'JOEY')我想我当时是十六岁
You know, I think I was 16.
('6-2', 'MONICA')求求你  只要剪后面一点点
Please, just a little bit off the back.
('6-3', 'PHOEBE')我还是坚持不要
I'm still on "no."
('6-4', 'RACHEL')早安
Morning.
('6-4', 'RACHEL')你们能不能闭一会儿眼睛
Could you close your eyes for a sec?
('6-5', 'JOEY')不  不  不  我可不要再上当
No, no, no. I'm not falling for that again.
('6-6', 'PHOEBE')怎么回事
What's going on?
('6-7', 'RACHEL')昨晚我做了一件蠢事
I sort of did a stupid thing last night.
('6-8', 'CHANDLER')你做了什么蠢事
What stupid thing did you do?
('6-9', 'PAOLO')大家早上好
Bon giorno tutti!
('6-9', 'PAOLO')好了  保罗
Okay, Paolo,
('7-1', 'RACHEL')大家你都见到了  他们也都见到你了
Now you've seen everybody and they've all seen you.
('7-2', 'MONICA')瑞秋  怎么回事
Rachel, how did this happen?
('7-3', 'RACHEL')我也不知道  只是昨晚凑巧碰到他
I don't know, I kind of ran into him last night.
('7-4', 'PHOEBE'),('7-5', 'RACHEL')-在哪里  -在他的公寓
,- Where? - At his apartment.
('7-5', 'RACHEL')这是果汁吗
Is this juice?
('7-6', 'JOEY')你忘了他勾引菲比  所以你才甩了他
And the fact that you dumped him because he hit on Phoebe?
('7-7', 'RACHEL')天啊  我真是可悲  我是个烂货
Oh, God, I know. I'm pathetic, I'm a loser.
('7-8', 'MONICA')甜心  你不可悲  你只是伤心
Honey, you're not pathetic. You're just sad.
('7-9', 'CHANDLER')大家伤心时都会干蠢事
People do stupid things when they're upset.
('7-10', 'MONICA')如果我和不该上床的人上床前都投硬币
My God, if I had a nickel for every guy I wish I hadn't
('7-10', 'MONICA')但这事关你的严重错误
But this is about your horrible mistake.
('7-11', 'ROSS')对不起  我们迟到了
Sorry we're late.
('7-11', 'ROSS')我们
We were....
('7-11', 'ROSS')肢体接触了一下
Well, there was touching.
('7-12', 'PAOLO')罗斯
Hey, Ross!
('7-13', 'ROSS')保罗
Hey, Paulo.
('7-13', 'ROSS')你
What a....
('7-13', 'ROSS')你在这里干什么
What are you doing here?
('7-14', 'PAOLO')跟瑞秋嘿咻
I do Raquel!
('7-15', 'ROSS')他回来了
So he's back?
('7-16', 'RACHEL')对  他回来了  有什么问题吗
Yeah, he's back. Is that a problem?
('7-17', 'ROSS')没问题
No, not a problem.
('7-18', 'RACHEL')很好  没有问题
Good. Glad it's not a problem.
('7-19', 'PHOEBE')你不许再碰我的屁股
You're gonna have to not touch my ass.
('7-20', 'CHANDLER')不管这美味的面包和浓厚的紧张气氛了
Despite the yummy bagels and palpable tension...
('7-20', 'CHANDLER')我要去改裤子了
I've got my pants need to be altered.
('7-21', 'JOEY')钱德勒  你见到弗兰基时  替我问个好
Chandler, when you see Frankie, tell him Joey Tribbiani says hello.
('7-21', 'JOEY')他会明白其中的意思
He'll know what it means.
('7-22', 'CHANDLER')你确定他能听懂这暗号吗
You sure he'll be able to crack that code?
('7-23', 'MONICA')上次保罗来这里时  我的短发要可爱多了
It's funny. The last time Paolo was here, my hair was so much shorter and cuter.
('7-24', 'PHOEBE')好吧
All right.
('7-24', 'PHOEBE')但你要保证不会指手画脚
But you have to promise that you will not be all controlly and bossy...
('7-24', 'PHOEBE')不会拿出摩妮卡的作风
...and all Monica about it.
('7-25', 'MONICA')我保证
I promise.
('7-26', 'PHOEBE')好  让我看看
All right, let's see.
('7-26', 'PHOEBE')你们有一些会被剪掉 有些不会
Now, some of you are gonna get cut and some of you aren't.
('7-26', 'PHOEBE')但我保证绝对不会痛
But I promise, none of you will feel a thing.
('8-1', 'PHOEBE'),('8-2', 'MONICA')-就这样吧  我不干了  -我什么都没说
,- That's it. I quit. - What? I didn't say anything!
('8-3', 'PHOEBE')但这不是一副信任的表情
But this isn't the face of a person who trusts a person.
('8-3', 'PHOEBE')这是一副
This is the face of a person who, you know...
('8-3', 'PHOEBE')不信任人的表情
...doesn't trust a person.
('8-4', 'MONICA')对不起  对不起
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
('8-4', 'MONICA')菲比  这比我们说的要短了一点
Phoebe.It's just a little shorter than what we had discussed.
('8-5', 'PHOEBE')你放轻松好吗  我知道要怎么剪
Would you relax? I know what I am doing.
('8-5', 'PHOEBE')他的发型就是这样
This is how he wears it.
('8-6', 'MONICA')谁的发型就是这样
How who wears it?
('8-7', 'PHOEBE')黛咪·摩儿
Demi Moore.
('8-8', 'MONICA')黛咪·摩儿不是男"他"
Demi Moore is not a "he."
('8-9', 'PHOEBE')他在《阔少爷》与《十全十美》都是男"他"
Well, he was a "he" in Arthur and in 10.
('8-10', 'MONICA')那是杜德利·摩尔
That's Dudley Moore!
('8-10', 'MONICA')我说我要黛咪·摩儿的发型
I said I wanted it like Demi Moore!
('8-12', 'MONICA')老天
Oh, my God!
('8-12', 'MONICA')天啊
('8-12', 'MONICA')我的天  真对不起
Oh, my God! I'm sorry!
('8-13', 'PHOEBE')黛咪·摩儿是哪一个
Which one is Demi Moore?
('8-14', 'MONICA')她演过《桃色机密》《桃色交易》和《人鬼情未了》
She's the actress that was in Disclosure, Indecent Proposal, Ghost!
('8-15', 'PHOEBE')她的头发非常美
She's got gorgeous hair.
('8-16', 'MONICA'),('8-16', 'MONICA')-我知道  -天呐
,- I know! - Oh, my god!
('9-1', 'FRANKIE')你的裤脚翻边要多长
How long do you want the cuffs?
('9-2', 'CHANDLER')至少要跟裤子一样长
At least as long as I have the pants.
('9-3', 'FRANKIE')我听懂了
I just got that.
('9-3', 'FRANKIE')好  现在要量内缝
Okay. Now we'll do your inseam.
('10-1', 'RACHEL')她情况怎么样
How is she?
('10-2', 'PHOEBE')还不好说
It's too soon to tell.
('10-2', 'PHOEBE')她在休息  这是好兆头
She's resting, which is a good sign.
('10-3', 'ROSS')头发怎么样
How's the hair?
('10-4', 'PHOEBE')我不想骗你  罗斯  不太理想
I'm not gonna lie to you. Ross. It doesn't look good.
('10-4', 'PHOEBE')我在一边夹上发夹  似乎能阻止卷曲
I put a clip on one side, which seems to have stopped the curling.
('10-5', 'JOEY')能不能看看她
Can we see her?
('10-6', 'PHOEBE')你的头发太好看了  会让她伤心
Your hair looks too good. I think it'd upset her.
('10-6', 'PHOEBE'),('10-6', 'PHOEBE')-罗斯  你去看看她好了  -好
,- Ross, you come on in. - Yeah.
('10-7', 'JOEY')你还好吗
Well, how you doing?
('10-9', 'JOEY')我很好
I'm okay.
('10-10', 'RACHEL'),('10-10', 'RACHEL')-这么糟糕  -怎么说
,- That bad, huh? - What?
('10-12', 'RACHEL')瑞秋  我可以感觉到女人的难过脆弱
Look, Rach, I can sense when women are depressed and vulnerable.
('10-12', 'RACHEL')这是我的天赋之一
It's one of my gifts.
('10-13', 'JOEY')乔伊  当我看到他和她一起下飞机
Joey, when I saw him get off that plane with her...
('10-14', 'RACHEL')我觉得我坠入了谷底
...I really thought I just hit rock bottom.
('10-15', 'JOEY')但今天是谷底
But today, it's like there's rock bottom...
('10-15', 'JOEY')下面还有五十尺厚的垃圾
... 50 feet of crap...
('10-15', 'JOEY')再下面才是我
...then me.
('10-16', 'CHANDLER')你必须告诉罗斯你的感受
You got to tell Ross how you feel.
('10-16', 'CHANDLER')我怎么能告诉他  朱莉呢
Come on, how can I just tell him? What about Julie?
('10-16', 'CHANDLER')管她干什么  他们才在一起两周
What about her? They've only been going out for two weeks.
('10-16', 'CHANDLER')罗斯已经爱你十年了
Ross has been in love with you for like 10 years.
('10-16', 'CHANDLER'),('10-16', 'CHANDLER')-我不知道  我不知道  -瑞秋  瑞秋
,- I don't know. I don't know. - Rache, Rache.
('10-16', 'CHANDLER')我交往过很多女人
I've been with my share of women.
('10-19', 'CHANDLER')我交往过很多别人的女人
I've been with a lot of people's share of women.
('10-21', 'JOEY')但重点是
But the point is...
('10-21', 'JOEY')我从来没有对任何人像罗斯对你这样专情
... I've never felt about anyone the way Ross felt about you.
('10-21', 'JOEY')真的吗
Really?
('10-21', 'JOEY')喂  老乡
Yo, paisan!
('10-21', 'JOEY')能聊聊吗
Can I talk to you for a sec?
('10-21', 'JOEY')你的裁缝
Your tailor...
('10-21', 'JOEY')是个大坏蛋
...is a very bad man!
('10-25', 'JOEY')弗兰基吗  你在说什么
Frankie? What are you talking about?
('10-25', 'JOEY')怎么了
Hey, what's going on?
('10-25', 'JOEY')乔伊的裁缝
Joey's tailor...
('10-25', 'JOEY')占了我的便宜
...took advantage of me.
('10-25', 'JOEY'),('10-25', 'JOEY')-什么  -不可能  我去他那里十二年了
,- What? - No way! I've been going to the guy for 12 years.
('10-25', 'JOEY')别扯了  他说要量我的内缝
Oh, come on! He said he was gonna do my inseam.
('10-27', 'JOEY')他的手沿着我的腿往上摸  然后就
Then he ran his hand up my leg and then there was definite
('10-27', 'JOEY')什么
What?
('10-27', 'JOEY')包住了
Cupping.
('11-2', 'ROSS')他们就是这样量裤子的
That's how they do pants!
('11-2', 'ROSS')首先量一边  把小弟弟推到一旁
First they go up one side, they move it over.
('11-4', 'CHANDLER')然后量另一边  把小弟弟推回来  然后量后面
Then they go up the other side, they move it back, then they do the rear.
('11-4', 'CHANDLER')怎么了  罗斯  裁缝量裤子不都是这样吗
What? Ross, tell him. Isn't that how a tailor measures pants?
('11-4', 'CHANDLER')是的  的确是这样  在监狱里
Yes, yes, it is. In prison!
('11-5', 'PHOEBE')你是怎么搞的
What's the matter with you?
('11-5', 'PHOEBE')什么
What?
('11-5', 'PHOEBE')不是这样吗
That's not?
('11-5', 'PHOEBE')我的老天
Oh, my God!
('11-5', 'PHOEBE')连玛丽·泰勒·摩尔的发型也比这个要好
Even Mary Tyler Moore would've been better.
('11-9', 'RACHEL')我喜欢
I like it.
('11-9', 'RACHEL')真的  我觉得"十全十美"
I do. I think it's a 10!
('11-9', 'RACHEL')谢谢
Thank you.
('11-9', 'RACHEL')我的头发很让人开怀
My hair is very amused.
('11-13', 'ROSS')莫妮卡  事情还可能更糟
Come on, Mon, things could be worse.
('11-14', 'RACHEL')你可能会被"困在纽约月光中"
You could "get caught between the moon and New York City.
('11-14', 'RACHEL')"我知道很疯狂  不过千真万确"
I know it's crazy, but it's true."
('11-15', 'ROSS')真够意思
Thank you.
('11-17', 'ROSS')我要走了  待会见
Well, I gotta go. Bye.
('11-17', 'ROSS')瑞秋  再见
Bye, Rach!
('11-17', 'ROSS')慢着  你要走了
Wait, are you leaving?
('11-17', 'ROSS')所以我才说再见
That's what I meant by "bye."
('11-17', 'ROSS'),('11-17', 'ROSS')-我能不能跟你说一下话  -好
,- Can I talk to you for a sec? - Okay.
('11-17', 'ROSS')医生检查疝气时
When the doctor does that hernia test....
('11-18', 'RACHEL')那很正常
That's okay.
('11-18', 'RACHEL')怎么啦
What's going on?
('12-1', 'JULIE')首先
Well, okay, first of all...
('12-4', 'PHOEBE')保罗和我没有在一起
... Paolo and I are not back together.
('12-4', 'PHOEBE')那是我干的一件蠢事
That was a stupid thing I did.
('12-4', 'PHOEBE')如果我能使时光倒转
If I could go back in time and do it again...
('12-4', 'PHOEBE')我绝对不会这么做
...well, I wouldn't.
('12-4', 'PHOEBE')其次
Second of all....
('12-4', 'PHOEBE')怎么了
What?
('12-4', 'PHOEBE')我要先问清楚
Before I said anything?I just need to know,
('12-5', 'RACHEL')你跟他分手后
is this one of those things where you break up with a guy...
('12-6', 'PHOEBE')我告诉你我的想法
... I tell you what I think...
('12-6', 'PHOEBE')你会不会第二天又和他重修旧好
...and the next day you get back together with the guy...
('12-6', 'PHOEBE')那我就会跟个大傻蛋一样了
...and I look like a complete idiot?
('12-6', 'PHOEBE')不不不
No, no, no, no, no.
('12-6', 'PHOEBE')好  我觉得他实在很烂
Well, then, I think the guy's scum.
('12-6', 'PHOEBE')我讨厌他  我真的很厌恶他
I hate him. I mean, I actually I physically hate him.
('12-6', 'PHOEBE')我一直很厌恶他
I always have.
('12-6', 'PHOEBE')你绝对该找个更好的男人
And you are way too good to be with a guy like that.
('12-6', 'PHOEBE')真的
Really?
('12-6', 'PHOEBE')一个真正能欣赏你的人才配得上你
You deserve to be with someone who appreciates you...
('12-6', 'PHOEBE')了解你有多么幽默
...and who gets how funny...
('12-6', 'PHOEBE')多么温柔  多么体帖
...and sweet and amazing...
('12-6', 'PHOEBE')多么美丽性感
...and adorable and sexy you are.
('12-6', 'PHOEBE')每天早上醒来都会想着
You know? Someone who wakes up every morning thinking:
('12-6', 'PHOEBE')天啊  我跟瑞秋在一起
"Oh, my God. I'm with Rachel!"
('12-6', 'PHOEBE')能让你舒心的人
You know? Someone who makes you feel good.
('12-6', 'PHOEBE')就像我与朱莉一样
Like the way I do with Julie.
('12-6', 'PHOEBE')你刚才是不是还有话要说
Was there a "second of all"?
('12-6', 'PHOEBE')不  我想我已经说完了
No, I think that was the whole "all."
('12-6', 'PHOEBE')我要走了
I gotta go.
('12-6', 'PHOEBE')不  我向天发誓  爸
No, I swear to God, Dad!
('12-6', 'PHOEBE')不是这样量裤子的
That's not how they measure pants!
('12-6', 'PHOEBE')我想要剪个短发  就像安迪·麦克道威尔的新发型
I was thinking of doing it shorter, like Andie MacDowell's haircut.
('12-6', 'PHOEBE'),('12-6', 'PHOEBE')-这我会剪  真的  -真的吗
,- Yeah, I could do that. Yes. - Really?
('12-6', 'PHOEBE'),('12-6', 'PHOEBE')-你要现在就剪吗  好  -太好了
,- You wanna do it now? Okay. - Great!
('12-6', 'PHOEBE')待会见
See you.
('12-6', 'PHOEBE')这次我要弄清楚
I just wanna make really sure this time.
('12-6', 'PHOEBE')安迪·麦克道威尔是《四个婚礼和一个葬礼》的女主角吗
Andie MacDowell is the girl from Four Weddings and a Funeral, right?
('12-6', 'PHOEBE')不是
No.
('12-6', 'PHOEBE')不不不
No, no, no, no, no.
('12-6', 'PHOEBE')那是罗迪·麦克道尔
That's Roddy McDowall.
('12-6', 'PHOEBE')安迪·麦克道威尔是演《人猿星球》的那个家伙
Andie MacDowell is the guy from Planet of the Apes.
('12-6', 'PHOEBE'),('12-6', 'PHOEBE')-对  -好
,- Oh, yes. - Okay.
('12-6', 'PHOEBE'),('12-6', 'PHOEBE')-谢谢  -别客气
,- Thank you. - You're welcome.